<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ToolSettings xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <SettingsVersion>1</SettingsVersion>
  <SupportableTools>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>FetchXML Builder</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>20</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>Plugin Trace Viewer</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>15</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>Bulk Data Updater</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>40</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>Latebound Constants Generator</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>30</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>UML Diagram Generator</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>30</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>Custom API Tester</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>30</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>Custom Action Tester</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>30</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
    <SupportableTool>
      <Name>Power Apps Checker</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ShowAutomatically>true</ShowAutomatically>
      <ShowAutoPercentChance>30</ShowAutoPercentChance>
    </SupportableTool>
  </SupportableTools>
  <ToastableTools>
    <ToastableTool>
      <Name>FetchXML Builder</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ExecuteStart>25</ExecuteStart>
      <ExecuteEnd>0</ExecuteEnd>
      <ExecuteInterval>50</ExecuteInterval>
      <ExecutePercentChance>100</ExecutePercentChance>
      <OpenPercentChance>80</OpenPercentChance>
      <MinMinutesBetweenToasts>60</MinMinutesBetweenToasts>
    </ToastableTool>
    <ToastableTool>
      <Name>Plugin Trace Viewer</Name>
      <Enabled>true</Enabled>
      <ExecuteStart>25</ExecuteStart>
      <ExecuteEnd>0</ExecuteEnd>
      <ExecuteInterval>50</ExecuteInterval>
      <ExecutePercentChance>80</ExecutePercentChance>
      <OpenPercentChance>50</OpenPercentChance>
      <MinMinutesBetweenToasts>60</MinMinutesBetweenToasts>
    </ToastableTool>
  </ToastableTools>
  <ShowMinutesAfterToolInstall>1440</ShowMinutesAfterToolInstall> <!-- 1 day -->
  <ShowMinutesAfterToolNewVersion>120</ShowMinutesAfterToolNewVersion> <!-- 2 hours -->
  <ShowMinutesAfterSupportingShown>760</ShowMinutesAfterSupportingShown> <!-- 2 days=2880, 1d=1440, 12h=760 -->
  <ShowMinutesAfterSubmitting>5760</ShowMinutesAfterSubmitting> <!-- 1 week=10080, 4d=5760 -->
  <ShowAutoPercentChance>40</ShowAutoPercentChance>
  <ShowAutoRepeatTimes>10000</ShowAutoRepeatTimes>
  <ResetUnfinalizedSupportingAfterDays>4</ResetUnfinalizedSupportingAfterDays>
  <BMACLinkPositionRandom>true</BMACLinkPositionRandom>
  <CloseLinkPositionRandom>true</CloseLinkPositionRandom>
  <HelpWhyText>Why Support the Tools You Use?

In the Power Platform community, some people create tools, others share ideas, write documentation, and fix bugs. Most simply use these tools—and that’s perfectly fine!

But think about it: when you watch TV or stream music, you pay for Netflix, Amazon Prime, or Spotify. Why? Because you value what you get.

Open-source tools are free to use, but they’re not free to build or maintain. If you benefit from them—saving time, improving quality—consider giving back. Support isn’t just about money; it’s about acknowledging the value you’ve received.

Especially if you work in a large corporation, using free tools to drive revenue, supporting the community is the right thing to do. It’s about fairness and sustainability.

You’re already part of the community by using these tools. Now you can support them formally—not just with a coffee donation, but in a way that helps development and maintenance.

Want to learn more? Read my thoughts here: https://jonasr.app/helping/

Let’s make “Conscienceware” a reality.

- Jonas Rapp</HelpWhyText>
  <HelpInfoText>Your entered name, company, country, email, and amount will not be stored in any official system. The information will only be saved in my personal Excel file and in my own Power Platform app, mostly for me, myself and I to learn even more about how the platform could help us. I also do this to ensure that you can get an invoice, and if needed, we can communicate by email.
The email you share with me, only to me, will never be sold to any company. I won't try to sell anything. Period.

You will receive an official receipt immediately and, if needed, an invoice. Supporting can be done with a credit card. Other options, such as Google Pay, will be available depending on your location. Stripe handles the payment.

When you click the big button here, the information you entered here will be included in the form on my website, jonasr.app, and a few hidden information: tool name, version, and your XrmToolBox 'InstallationId' (a random Guid generated the first time you use the toolbox). If you are curious, you can see how to find your ID on this link: https://jonasr.app/xtb-finding-installationid.

Since I would like to be very clear and transparent, we store your XrmToolBox InstallationId on a server to ensure that this installation supports it in some way. There is nothing about your name, the amount, or the contribution. I am not interested in hacking this information.

The button in the top-right corner opens this info. You can also right-click on it and find more options, especially:
* I have already supported this tool — use this to tell me that you already support this tool in some way, so that this pop-up prompt will not ask you again.
* I will never support this tool — use it if you think it is a bad idea, and you probably won't use the tool again; it won't ask you again.

For questions, contact me at https://jonasr.app/contact.</HelpInfoText>
</ToolSettings>
